{"response_code": 0, "results": [{"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "&quot;Half-Life 2&quot; runs on the Source Engine.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "In World of Warcraft lore, Thrall is the original wielder of &quot;Doomhammer&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "The Sniper&#039;s SMG in Team Fortress 2, was originally intended to be the Scout&#039;s primary weapon.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "In Riot Games &quot;League of Legends&quot; the name of Halloween event is called &quot;The Reckoning&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In Pok&eacute;mon, Arbok evolves into Seviper.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Valve&#039;s &quot;Portal&quot; and &quot;Half-Life&quot; franchises exist within the same in-game universe.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "In &quot;Call Of Duty: Zombies&quot;, you can upgrade the &quot;Apothicon Servant&quot; in the &quot;Shadows Of Evil&quot; map.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "&quot;Return to Castle Wolfenstein&quot; was the only game of the Wolfenstein series where you don&#039;t play as William &quot;B.J.&quot; Blazkowicz.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "In the Season One Championship of &quot;League of Legends&quot;, the highest achievable rank was Diamond.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The shotgun appears in every numbered Resident Evil game.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]}